sae.net 2014-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Sigma Alpha Epsilon

#### Use of Links

Throughout our web pages, we provide links to other servers that may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views or accuracy of the information contained on other servers.

Creating a text link from your website to our site does not require permission. If you have a link you'd like us to consider adding to our website, send an e-mail to [webmaster@sae.net](mailto:webmaster@sae.net) with the subject "Link Request."

#### Use of Text and Images

If you would like to publish information that you find on our website, please send your request to [webmaster@sae.net](mailto:webmaster@sae.net). Where text or images are posted on our site with the permission of the original copyright holder, a copyright statement appears at the bottom of the page.

Information about using our logo and images is available by contacting the communications department at (847) 475-1856.

#### Accessibility

This website is designed to be accessible to visitors with disabilities and to comply with federal guidelines concerning accessibility. We welcome your comments. If you have suggestions on how to make the site more accessible, please contact us at [webmaster@sae.net](mailto:webmaster@sae.net).

#### Credit Card Refund Policy

Requests for membership dues refunds must be made in writing and directed to [mkilb@sae.net](mailto:mkilb@sae.net). SAE's policy is not to refund membership dues; the organization shall do so on a case by case basis upon approval of the appropiate personnel. Donations may be refunded if processed in error; please contact [Foundation@sae.net](mailto:Foundation@sae.net) for more information or assistance.

SAE reserves the right to modify this Refund Policy at its discretion, or against any customer it believes is abusing this policy.  Any such revision or change will be binding and affective immediately after posting of the revised Refund Policy on SAE's website.

#### Website Privacy Policy

We have created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website.

#### Reading or Downloading

We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or princeton.edu if you are connecting from Princeton University's domain), the date and time you access our site and the internet address of the website from which you linked to our site.

We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.

#### Online Profile Updates and Donations

If you complete the profile update form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings. See the "Opt Out" section below.

#### Sending Us an E-Mail

You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from e-mail primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer you questions. We may also use your e-mail to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.

We want to be very clear. We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.

If you sign up for one of our e-mail lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We won't share your name or e-mail address with any outside parties.

#### Children and Privacy

For children who visit our site, special rules apply. We do not request personal information about children, such as first and last name or street address and city. When children send e-mail to us, their online contact information (e-mail address) is not used to re-contact them and is not maintained in retrievable form.

#### Opt-Out or Change Your Contact Information

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us through a special online form. You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. You may also update your contact information previously provided to us through another online form. You cannot remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication. To change your subscription status, send us an e-mail at [webmaster@sae.net](mailto:webmaster@sae.net).

#### Questions about Our Policies

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at:

1856 Sheridan Road  
Evanston, Illinois 60201-3837  
(847) 475-1856
